

## **Summary**

A dedicated, hard working individual. Reliable and attentive when working in groups during pre-production and post production as well as on set, capable of problem solving in the work place when it comes to last minute alterations and able to take lead when needing to and able to use leadership skills effectively in group work. Wanting to work within the Creative Media industry, specialising in Writing and Editing. However, willing to take on any role within a production team. Able to provide reflective feedback about others and personal work, written and vocally narrated in a one-to-session or group work. An ideas person that can produce creative and reasonable ideas on the spot and also during

# **Employment**

National Lottery Heritage Funding

**Bolton University** 

Paid employment.
Taking on leading editing job to create two separate promotional videos demonstrating where the money paid to National Lottery goes and what it helps to create

Bill Naughton Documentary

Oct 2017 to Current, Oct 2017 to Current

Oct 2017 to Current, Oct 2017 to Current Deld employment. Taking on the lead editor position within this project. Using stills, archive footage to create a 20 minute documentary that will go ahead to become a DVD in the future.

**Core Post** 

Work placement at an editing company within Media City, Manchester,

Clarks Ormskirk

Ormskirk

Sales Assistant and trained in children's shoe fittings. The roll included customer services, stock checking, and handling money. I was assigned on a company course to special in fitting and properly measure and fit for the customer needs.

# **Projects**

Bill Naughton Documentary

I have undertaken an editing position for the Documentary of Bill Naughton's success. This film will be featured on a DVD and sold in a mus

**Art Fyhibition Film** 

During this project, I was asked to undertake an editing position and edit an abstract/artistic piece of film for promotional use for the University of Bolton, Art, and Design

National Heritage Lottery Funding

National
In this project, I undertook a leading editing position alongside a colleague in which we were asked to edit two short pieces of film for promotional reas
Lottery Heritage Funding.

7 is a photography project I took on myself as an experiment in trying to find my style in photography, more specifically, street photography. I also edited the photographs myself and proceeded to share them across my social media as well.

This was a photography project I took on myself outside of education, in which I went on a trip to Berlin and took photographs, then proceeded to edit the photographs to my liking and sharing them on social media

Filming of a student council meeting to be used to promote the college and student council scheme

**Student Council Meeting** 

Taking on the Directing, camera operator and editor positions on this project to produce a music video for the song 'Photograph'.

'Photograph' Music Video

Filming footage of Remembrance Day Parade in Southport. Footage was used to support local fundraising for the Poppy Appeal.

Remembrance Day Parade Southport College Fashion Show

Filming local students fashion show at Southport College, used to promote the college fashion design course

Farmaggedon Short Clip/Interviews

Filming a short clip that suited the Horror theme of the attraction for a display, edited together using Final Cut Pro. With a small team, during the time at the attraction, we also

### **Activities**

Photo/Video Editor 2015 to Current

## **Volunteering**

PASS Leadership · PASS Leader University of Bolton

Sep 2016 to Nov 2016

University on Duttuin
Having been invited to take part in PASS, and PASS Leaders training before ongoing with the PASS Session Leading other students, facilitating them with queries about the
university and the Media course they are attending, guiding the students in the right direction when it comes to course work and helping them with any topic within the course
that they are having difficulty understanding and working on.

Core Post Work Experience · Assistant

Nov 2017 to Nov 2017

During this work placement, I got the opportunity to shadow editors in their place of work to understand the work environment they work in and the way they work, as well as understand the software they use and techniques in which each individual editor

### **Contact**

g.bond28@yahoo.co.uk

http://gbond28.wixsite.com/georgiabondportfolio

**C** 07583 159620

### **Education**

#### University of Bolton

University of Unitude
BA Honors Media, Writing & Production 2018
This is a highly creative and challenging BA Honours Degree in a Media course that covers all aspects of pre-production, filming and porty by the production as well. This course also covers aspects of reactive writing for both, TV and Film, planning and producing scripts for both television and cinema.

### **Skills**

#### SOFTWARE

Premier Pro CC

Final Cut Pro

Photoshop After Effects

Lightroom

#### CAMERA & SOUND

live shooting

Cinematography

Use of Canon 700D

Use of Sony Camera

#### WRITING

TV Episode Short Film

Feature Film

Radio Drama **Short Stories**